

pimkinaanastasiia@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/pimkina/



https://github.com/Anastsiia

ANASTASIIA PIMKIN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Highly motivated young software engineer with humble (3+ years) but pretty intensive experience and a master's degree in Computer Science. Possesses not only strong basic knowledge in the field, deep OOP understanding and passion for solving complicated coding puzzles, but also effective communication skills, a strong sense of responsibility, and a dedicated work ethic.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

AR Layers, LLC (Israel), 2022-2023

- Developed an innovative AR application using Python, C# and Unity for Android.
- Developed a custom **C# library** to streamline communication with the **back-end API**, optimizing data exchange and enhancing the Unity application's functionality.
- Successfully integrated and customized Google API and Mapbox SDK to optimize app functionality, ensuring seamless navigation and location-based features.
- Implemented **automated unit testing** achieving 95% code coverage.
- Contributed significantly to the application's architecture and data models.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Alfa-bank, JSC (Russia), 2022

- Developed and deployed 3D mini-games using Unity and C#.
- Collaborated in a high-performing C# automation development team that reduced manual workload by 40%.
- Managed Jenkins for streamlined development, reducing build and deployment times.
- Successfully integrated specific bank APIs and databases for loan approval application.
- Played an integral role in the production maintenance team, identifying and fixing issues.
- Significantly contributed to project efficiency by clearing 30% of the backlog.

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Customertimes, LLC (Russia), 2020-2022

- Developed new features for clients' desktop applications using Pega and C#.
- Conducted **testing and debugging** of both legacy and relevant functionality.
- Played a key role in **UI design** and Pega Cosmos UI customization.
- Created internal **C# libraries** for enhanced code reuse, optimizing development efficiency and promoting consistent application standards.

EDUCATION

ÉCOLE 42

2021-2022

Software engineering

THE KOSYGIN STATE UNIVERSITY OF RUSSIA

2011-2017

Computer Science, Master degree (GPA 4.8/5)

SKILLS

- C/C++
- C# (.NET)
- Unity
- Git
- SQL
- OOP
- Algorithms
- Data structures
- Unix shell

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian ★ ★ ★ ★

Russian 🜟 🛨

English $\star \star \star \star$

Chinese \star

Hebrew 🗡

COURSES

ITVDN

C# Starter

Pega Academy

Senior System Architect

System Architect

Udemy

Practical course for

beginners in SQL

Unity

Junior Programmer

mission

